# Ben Rhouma Rassil.benrhouma@esprit.tn +216 52 497 659 Route Tayeb Mhiri Aouina, Tunis



### **Interests**

I worked as part-time coach in a start-up teaching (HTML, JavaScript, CSS, NodeJS, Angular, Spring Boot) and I worked as a freelancer, for years, on several projects (analyze, design, development, deployment) using several languages and technologies (NodeJS, Angular, JEE, Spring Boot, Php ,...) and deployed them myself (Amazon EC2, jenkins, Docker ,Apache ,Nginx,...) and this introduced me, to the professional life meaning to be in contact with customers (gathering information and extract the needs) and deliver an optimized product ready for the production.

## **Education**

#### **BACCALAUREATE DIPLOMA**

2012

Computer Science, with grade "Good"

# BACHELOR DEGREE 2014-2017

Computer Science

# MASTER'S DEGREE 2017-2020

Computer Science - Software Engineering 2017-2020

## **Apps**

#### Web

Medical Service Web Laravel , php Security club website Angular, Symfony Student Platform Symfony , JavaFX, Android Survey WebSite Spring Boot, Angular8

#### Mobile

Visit Card Scanner **Android, OpenCV, Tesseract** Weather application **Ionic** 

#### Deskton

Virtual ATM Machine **JavaFX, MySQL** Stock Management system **JavaFX, MySQL** 

## **Experience**

## PROJECT LEADER April 2020 - Present Laevitas.ch

Data analysis platform based on quantitative finance models for the crypto-asset market.

NodeJS, NestJS, Python, Angular, MongoDB Stack, Mysql, AWS FC2

# FULL STACK JS DEVELOPER April 2019 - April 2020 SURECRETE CONSTRUCTION - SURE-BID.COM

Platform that Brings real construction projects to the SubContractors where they can discuss and make sure to bid on the right auction.

NodeJS, Angular, MongoDB Stack, AWS EC2

## JEE DEVELOPER November 2018 - Mars 2019 OTDAY ORGANIZATION

The Tunisian Organization of copyrights and related rights (OTDAV) is a public institution responsible for collective management of copyrights and related rights..

JEE , WildFly , MySql

# PHP WEB DEVELOPER July 2017 - October 2018 EFRICA ECOMMERCE

African E-commerce website dedicated for the artisans around africa to promote and sell their product.

PHP, Symfony, MySql

